pitstopmedia.com 2016-11-05

# Pitstop Media Inc - Privacy Policy

|  |  |   | 

195% Increase in AdWords CTR, Campaign Cost Decrease by 40%

Food Connect hired us to optimize an AdWords account with poor Quality Scores, high CPC and lack of any form of conversion tracking. Even then, we delivered ...

| 

### Privacy Policy Pitstop Media  
  
---  
  
#### What information do we collect?   
  
We collect information from you when you browse, visit, register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or blog, respond to a survey, and fill out a form to contact us or when you email us. 

When using our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter data such as, but not limited to, your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and company name.

Google Analytics - Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to track your website usage. Google sends one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including tracking user trends, such as how people browse our site. Google also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web and on Google services. If you wish to opt out from being tracked with Google Analytics please visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

ClickTale - Our site uses ClickTale web analytics service. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as any text you type in our website. ClickTale does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in our website. For more information on ClickTale privacy policy and how to opt-out please visit [http://www.clicktale.com/privacy](http://www.clicktale.com/privacy-policy)

Crazy Egg - Crazy Egg uses customized Java script tracking code to track information about our website visitors’ activity. This information is then stored on the Crazy Egg website for analysis and producing reports. For more information on Crazy Egg privacy policy and how to opt-out please visit <http://www.crazyegg.com/privacy>

Tynt – we use Tynt scripts in order to analyze and track content copied from our website. For more information on Crazy Egg privacy policy and how to opt-out please visit [http://www.tynt.com/company/privacy-policy/](http://www.tynt.com/privacy_policy.php)  

#### What do we use your information for?   
  
Any information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails (the email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions).

#### How do we protect your information?  
  
Your private information (names, phone number, company name, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers, so there is no way for a third party to access them from outside of Pitstop Media.  

#### Do we use cookies?  
  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers' hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow cookies) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract third-party service providers to assist us with better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

#### Third party links   
  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  

#### Online Privacy Policy Only  
  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  

#### Terms and Conditions   
  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section regarding the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.pitstopmedia.com/terms-of-use.php>  

#### Your Consent  
  
By using our site, you consent to our [website privacy policy](http://www.pitstopmedia.com/privacy-policy.php).  

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy   
  
If we make changes to our privacy policy, the changes will be posted on this page.   

#### Contacting Us  
  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.pitstopmedia.com  
202B-8322 130TH ST  
Surrey, BC V3W 8J9  
Canada  
office@pitstopmedia.com  
+1-800-617-4094
